Ready?
- 준비됐지?
- 그래
Hi, it's Rachel and Phoebe's.
Please...
- 안녕하세요
- 여기는
- 레이첼
- 그리고
피비의 집입니다
- 신호음이
- 울리면
-Leave..
-Leave.
울리면
But I just said "leave."
'울리면'은 내가 했어
좋은 단어는 네가 다 하잖아
I know because you have
all the good words.
난 뭐야, '여기는'
'그리고' 같은 것 뿐이야
What do I get? I get "it's," "and."
Oh, I'm sorry, I have "a." Forget it.
피비, 별것도 아니잖아
-That's silly.
-All right. So let's switch.
그럼 바꾸자
싫어, 내가 좋은 단어 할래
No, I have all the good words.
Okay, fine, fine.
We can switch.
알았어, 바꾸자
- 그래
- 좋아
- Hi...
-everybody...
안녕하세요
- 여러분
- 여기는
-It's...
-Rachel...
- 레이첼
- 그리고
-and...
-Phoebe's.
피비의 집입니다
Wait. How did you do that?
신호음이... 잠깐
어떻게 한 거야?
What?
뭘?
너 보통 룸메이트가 아니구나
Oh, you're no ordinary roommate,
are you?
This is gonna be interesting.
재미있어지겠다
Can we finish this later?
I'm going running before it gets dark.
이거 나중에 하면 안 될까?
해지기 전에 조깅해야 돼
참! 너도 같이 가자
-Why don't you come with me?
-Really?
진짜?
그래, 즐겁게 공원을
함께 뛰면서
It'll be fun! We'll run in the park.
It'll be our roommate-bonding thing.
룸메이트끼리
유대감을 쌓는 거야
좋아, 가자
Okay, let's go running!
게다가 멋진 남자도 많아
-There's cute guys there.
-Let's run towards them!
- 남자들을 향해 가자
- 좋아
잠깐만 있어 봐
Wait just one more second.
Hi, it's Phoebe and Rachel's.
Please leave a message. Thanks!
피비와 레이첼의 집입니다
메시지 남기세요, 고마워요
잠깐, 혼자 다 말한 거야?
Wait a minute.
You took all the words!
적수를 만난 거야, 레이첼 그린
You've met your match, Rachel Greene!
The One Where Phoebe Runs
방금 재미있는 책을 읽었어
I just finished this
fascinating book.
By the year 2030,
there'll be computers...
다가오는 2030년에는
컴퓨터가 실제 인간의 뇌와
비슷한 능력을 갖게 된대
that can carry out the same amount
of functions as a human brain.
이론적으로만 보면 네 생각과
기억을 컴퓨터에 저장시켜서
So, theoretically,
you could download...
your thoughts and memories
into this computer...
영원히 살 수 있는 거야
하나의 기계로서
and live forever as a machine.
And I just realized I can sleep
with my eyes open.
이제 보니 나
눈뜨고도 잘 수 있다
- 나 왔어
- 어서 와
Honey, it was a great idea,
nailing the boxes to the floor.
자기야, 바닥에 못질해둔
박스 진짜 멋지다
-I didn't nail the boxes to the floor.
-So you can move them!
난 박스 못질한 적 없는데?
그럼 옮길 수 있겠네?
And while I'm doing that, Ross has
a great computer story for you.
그동안 로스한테 신나는
컴퓨터 얘기나 듣고 있어
Hey, everybody!
I'd like you to meet Janine.
얘들아, 재닌을 소개할게
내 룸메이트가 될 거야
She's gonna be my new roommate!
- 안녕하세요
- 반가워요
나랑 같이 산대
And she's gonna live with me!
It's nice to meet you. Janine...?
만나서 반가워요
성이 어떻게 되죠?
르 크르와예요
재닌 르 크르와
Le Croix.
나도 몰랐는데
성도 정말 예쁘네요
I didn't know that.
What a pretty last name.
고향은 어디신데요?
So where are you from?
호주예요
몇 주전에 왔어요
Australia.
I just moved here.
From the land down under?
- 지구 반대편에서?
- 그래요
I didn't know that either!
그것도 몰랐는데
근데 무슨 일을 하시죠?
So what do you do?
-I'm a dancer.
-You're a dancer?
- 댄서예요
- 댄서라고요?
She's a dancer!
댄서란다 야
전 이만 가서 짐 풀게요
I think I'll go unpack.
잠깐만
고마워요
조이?
왜?
Did you interview her
before you asked her to move in?
이사 오라고 하기 전에
면접이나 제대로 했니?
물론 했지
Of course!
What did you ask her?
정확히 뭘 물었는데?
When can you move in?
'언제 들어오실래요?'
Thank you for bringing her
into our lives.
저런 여자를 찾아줘서
정말 고맙다
눈 튀어나오겠군
Unbelievable.
Down, boy.
진정하게나
Oh, no, no, no. She's not my type.
Not for me, she's not my type. She's too..
오해하지 마
내 취향이 아냐
뭐랄까, 나한테는 너무...
예쁘고 늘씬하고 섹시한
배꼽 노출녀다?
Beautiful, tall, sexy,
showing her stomach?
와, 박스 엄청 많네
Look at all the boxes!
조만간 데이트 신청해야지
I cannot wait to ask her out.
Wait a minute.
You can't. She's your roommate.
잠깐, 조이
룸메이트한테
데이트를 신청한다고?
It'll be too complicated.
그럼 너무 복잡해져
Yeah, don't do it.
맞아, 그러지 마
네가 사귀면
난 못 사귀잖아
I mean, if you date her,
then I can't date her.
What if you started going out with her
and it didn't work out?
데이트를 시작했다
깨지는 날엔 어떡하지?
그땐 내가 나서야지
That's when I make my move.
Remember when you broke up
with Donna...
도나랑 헤어지고 어떻게 됐냐
슈퍼마켓에서 마주치면
얼마나 끔찍했는지 기억나?
how horrible it was when you
bumped into her at the supermarket?
세상에, 맞다
Oh, God, yeah.
네가 그 슈퍼마켓에서
산다고 생각해봐
Now imagine you live
at the supermarket.
좋지
Okay!
그게 아냐
맞아, 그렇지
You're right! I don't want that.
I can't date her.
그럼 곤란해
이래선 못 사귀지
그 집적거리는 버릇도 고쳐
집안에선 문제가 될 거야
You'd better watch the flirting too,
because it could be trouble.
그건 힘들어
Well, that's gonna be tough, Mon.
난 매력적인 여자 앞에서
점잔빼는 일은 죽어도 못해
It's hard for me to be around
an attractive woman and not flirt.
You're around me all the time,
and you don't flirt.
나랑 있을 땐 안 그러잖아?
그래서 슬펐어, 귀염둥이?
A little sad about that, sweetie?
I have to tie my shoes, so you
go ahead. I'll catch up.
신발 끈 풀렸다
먼저 가, 따라갈게
- 알았어
- 그래
Come on, that's not running!
Let's go!
그것도 뛰는 거냐? 가자!
피비가 뛰면 영락없이
I'm telling you, when she runs...
개구리 커미트랑
6백만 불의 사나이 합체야
she looks like Kermit the Frog...
and the Six Million Dollar Man.
Monica had such a crush on him.
모니카가 그 남자
무지 좋아했는데
She used to kiss his poster
every night before she went to bed.
자기 전에 꼭 포스터에
뽀뽀를 했었지
나도 그랬어
I used to do that too!
Did you also have his album,
"It's Not Easy Being Green"?
그 사람 앨범도 있겠네?
'그린으로 살긴 힘들어'
Oh, Mon.
오, 모니카...
So Phoebe runs weird, huh?
피비 뛰는 게 이상하다고?
그래, 피비는 계속 하려는
눈치인데 어떻게 거절하지?
Yeah. And I know she'll
want to run again.
I don't know how to get out of it.
I mean, I live with her.
같이 사는 처지에
Why don't you be straight with her?
Tell her the truth.
그냥 솔직하게
있는 그대로 말해
You're right.
I should just tell her the truth.
맞아
사실대로 말해야겠다
- 얘들아
- 어서 와
Phoebe, Monica tripped me. I don't
think I can ever run again, ever!
피비, 모니카가 내 발을 걸어서
두 번 다시 조깅 못하게 생겼다
But we were having so much fun.
All those cute guys were checking us out.
그게 얼마나 재미있었는데
남자들 눈길도 듬뿍 받으면서
알아, 그 이글거리는 시선들
I know. They were definitely staring.
Why? Why would you do that?
왜 그런 짓을 한 거야?
I don't know.
모르겠어
Rachel, I'm sorry I hurt your ankles.
양쪽 발목이
다 삐어서 어떡하니
-Ankle.
-We'll see.
한쪽이야
두고 봐
자, 드디어 짐을 다 풀었다
도와줘서 고마워
Okay. I am officially unpacked.
Thanks for helping me, man.
조이?
Joe?
Well, I guess Joey went home.
조이는 귀가했구나
And look, there is still one box
I have to unpack.
저런, 아직 박스가
하나 더 남았네
I got you!
놀랐지롱!
Oh, my God, you almost gave me
a heart attack.
깜짝이야
심장이 멎을 뻔했어요
It was so hard not to laugh.
웃음 참느라 죽는 줄 알았다
Hey, the place looks great.
이런, 정말 근사하다
Not bad, right?
그런 대로 괜찮지?
모니카가 오늘 야근인데
Monica's working late,
so I'm gonna make this place spotless.
여길 번쩍번쩍하게
만들어 놓겠어
You know what else I'll do?
그 뿐만이 아냐
I'm gonna go downstairs
and get her some flowers.
내려가서 꽃을 사다놔야지
Who wouldn't want to live with me?
나랑 살기 싫은 사람 나와 봐
I don't.
저요
No, I want to live with
the super-hot Australian dancer!
난 새끈한 호주 댄서랑 살래
How's that going? Are you okay
with the not-flirting thing?
어때, 그 말버릇
단속 잘하고 있냐?
아직은 괜찮지만 너무 힘들다
So far. But it's tough.
기운이 자꾸 뻗치는데
해소할 방법이 없어
I've got this built-up flirting energy,
and I don't know how to get rid of it.
How you doing?
안녕하쇼
Get out!
나가!
Oh, man!
어머나
미안해요, 방이 너무 좁아서
Sorry. There's just
more room out here.
아니에요, 그러고 보니
나도 운동할 시간이군요
No, you just reminded me
that I have to do my stretches too.
Why don't you try to be...?
그게 아니고...
왜 그래요?
-What's wrong?
-Nothing.
아니에요
I didn't want you to touch me...
내 몸 만지지 말아요
운동하느라 땀투성이니까
because I'm all sweaty
from the workout.
샤워나 해야겠네요
I'm gonna hit the shower.
Oh, my God!
맙소사
Sorry about that stuff
hanging in there.
그런 걸 널어놔서 미안해요
끈팬티는 건조기에 못 넣어요
It's just my thongs are
too delicate for the dryer.
안녕
그래, 나야
Oh, yeah, it's me.
아침에 조깅화 꺼내들고
몰래 빠져나가는 거 봤어
I saw you grab your running shoes
this morning and sneak out.
You lied so you could run by yourself.
혼자 뛰려고 거짓말했지?
아냐, 피비
실은 그게 아니라...
No, Phoebe, no. I was....
그냥 확인 좀 해본 거야
I was actually just checking...
to see...
if I could run. And I can!
달릴 수 있는지,
달려도 되겠다!
Please, I'm not an idiot.
관둬라, 난 바보가 아냐
No, wait. Phoebe?
잠깐만, 피비...
같이 사는 커플은
정말 닮아가나 보다
Wow. Couples who live together
do start to look alike.
I am working right now. So say what you
have to say and leave me alone!
지금 바빠, 무슨 말을 해도
좋은데 나만 건드리지 마
말투까지 비슷하고
Sound alike too.
그래, '몬들러'야
So, Mondler....
What are you doing?
이게 대체 뭐하는 짓이지?
뭐긴 뭐야, 청소하잖아
What does it look like?
I am cleaning.
Did you get Monica's authorization
to move all her stuff?
모니카 허락이나 받고
세간을 다 들어낸 거야?
허락이 왜 필요해
다시 돌려놓을 거야
I don't need that.
I'll put everything back.
정확히 제자리를 찾아서?
Put it back exactly
where you found it?
그래, 정확히 제자리를
찾아서 돌려놓겠어
Yes. I'm gonna put it back
exactly where I found it.
First of all,
that attitude is not helping.
먼저 그런 태도는
전혀 도움이 안 돼
She won't care if I put her stuff
back in the same stupid place.
다 제자리에 갖다 놓으면
신경 안 쓸 거야
Hello? Did you just meet Monica?
여보셔? 당신 모니카
방금 만났습니까?
She'll recognize
that I did a nice thing...
걔는 내 자상함에 감동하고
또 고마워할 거야
and appreciate it.
일이 아주 잘 풀리겠다
Actually, this will work out well.
Because when you move back
with Joey...
넌 조이 집으로 돌아가고
Joey's hot new roommate
can come live with me.
조이의 새 룸메이트는
나랑 살면 되니까
Oh, I see. You're trying
to freak me out.
알았다, 겁주려는 거지?
Chandler, Monica is really weird
about this kind of stuff, all right?
잘 들어, 모니카는 이런 일에
병적으로 집착하는 애야
16년을 같이 산 내가 보증하지
걔 필시 까무러친다니까
Believe me, I lived with her for
16 years. She's going to freak out.
Oh, my God.
She's going to sit on you.
일났다, 널 깔고 앉을 텐데
That probably won't hurt as much anymore.
예전처럼 아프진 않겠지만
그렇지 않아
내가 증명해주지
No, she is not.
I'll prove it to you.
당장 전화 걸게
I'll call her right now.
Phone's done.
전화기 청소 끝
- 여보세요
- 모니카, 어때?
-Hey, Mon. How's it going?
-Terrible.
끔찍해
내 손이 안 가면 되는 게 없어
일 망치려고 작당들을 했나 봐
If I want something done right,
I have to do it myself.
Other people just wreck stuff.
오늘밤에 살인날지도 몰라
I think I might kill someone tonight.
설마 그렇게 심각하려고
Come on, it can't be that bad.
정말이야
The only thing getting me through...
곧 자기 본다는 낙으로
어떻게 버티고는 있어
is knowing I'll see you soon.
- 일찍 들어갈까 봐
- 안 돼, 그럼 안 되지
I might even try
to get out of here early.
자기가 빠지면
되는 일이 없다면서
It sounds like they need you there.
- 오빠 거기 왔어?
- 여긴 아주 좋아, 이따 봐
-You're just hanging out with Ross?
-It's all good! Okay, bye!
내 생명이 위태롭다
She's gonna kill me.
수화기 거꾸로 놨어
The phone was facing the other way.
이건 위로 올라가야지
And that goes back up there.
This is good. This is under control.
We should start with the big stuff.
어떻게든 수습을 해보자
이렇게 하는 거야
큰 것부터 시작하자고
그래야 일이 쉽지
그럼 이 소파부터
That'll be the easiest.
Let's start with the couch.
제가 하죠
I got it.
That doesn't look right.
이건 좀 이상한데?
무슨 소리야
카펫이랑 정확히 맞잖아
What are you talking about?
The couch is in line with the carpet.
이쪽으로 살짝 돌아가서
다리를 턱하니 올려놓으면...
Then I can just walk over here
and casually put my feet up on....
Okay, here's what we do.
좋아, 이 정도야 뭐
소파를 커피테이블에 대자
We move the couch
closer to the coffee table.
어허, 그럼 소파 뒷면이
카펫이랑 안 맞잖아
But then the back of the couch
won't line up with the carpet.
Well, we'll just move
the coffee table...
좋아, 그럼 커피테이블을
소파 쪽으로 미는 거지
closer to the couch.
아냐, 그럼 커피테이블이
착석구역 중앙에서 벗어나
But then the coffee table
won't be centered in the seating area.
But the coffee table doesn't
match the table!
그럼 커피테이블이
거시기 하잖아, 로스야
얘들아, 들어봐
Look, what am I gonna do?
어떡하면 좋지?
I'm not flirting, but I'm drawing
her to me like a moth to a flame!
난 아무 짓도 안 했는데
재닌이 불나방처럼
나한테 달려들잖아
What the hell's going on over here?
이건 또 무슨 사태야
Monica's gonna kill you!
넌 모니카한테 죽었다
I need your help.
너희들이 좀 도와줘
I have to do something
to repel this woman.
어떻게든 이 여자를
떨어뜨려야겠어
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
잠깐, 그렇지
You guys repel women all the time!
너희한텐 여자가
붙어나질 않잖아
Hey, I've been married three times.
난 세 번이나 결혼한 몸이야
아니, 그런 경우 많았어
No, I've seen it happen.
You get a rapport going with a woman,
but somehow you manage to kill it.
어떻게 잘 돼 가는 듯하다가도
너흰 그거 죽 쑤는 데 선수잖아
Time after time after time after time.
계속해서, 반복해서
거듭해서, 지속적으루다
What's your secret?
비결이 뭐냐?
We do not repel women, okay?
우리한테 여자가 안 붙긴!
말도 안 되는 소리 그만둬
That is completely untrue.
Oh, yes, we do, my man.
그건 사실이야, 친구
Remember when we went to a dance...
대학 봄 축제 무도회 때
네가 찍어둔 여자애한테 가서
and you walked up to that girl
you liked and talked...
아일랜드의 감자 기근
얘기만 했던 거 생각나?
about the lrish potato famine?
What about you?
You weren't so hot either.
넌 어떻고, 너도 대학 때
잘 나갔던 건 아니잖아
After everything he said,
he'd go..
말끝마다 이랬어
'버럼범 피시'
Monica doesn't like that either.
I should stop doing that.
모니카도 싫어하더라
아무래도 그만해야겠다
Girls don't like it when
I start talking about science.
또 있다
여자들은 과학 얘기를
꺼내면 싫어해
That's not specific to girls.
여자들만 그런 거 아냐
This is great. What else?
그거 아주 좋다
또 뭐가 있지?
문법 따지는 것도 싫어해
They don't like you correcting
their grammar.
And they don't like it when you
explain why your jokes are funny.
농담해놓고 왜 웃기는지
설명하는 것도 밥맛이야
They don't like it when you
keep asking them if they like you.
자기를 좋아하냐고
집요하게 물어보는 것도
-Man, I am so lucky I have Monica.
-I'm never gonna find love again.
모니카가 내 옆에
붙어있는 게 기적이군
난 이제 연애 못할 거야
왔니?
-Can I talk to you for a second?
-Sure.
우리 얘기 좀 할까?
그래
좋아
난...
Phoebe, I just wanted to say
I'm sorry, okay?
피비, 너한테 사과하고 싶어
내가 생각을 잘못했어
거짓말한 것도 그렇고
I handled the situation horribly.
And I should not have lied to you.
So what should you have done?
그럼 어떡해야 되는데?
I should have told you the truth.
솔직하게 말했어야지
어허, 그게 뭐지?
Which is?
Well, the reason I didn't
want to go running with you is...
그게...
너랑 같이 뛰기 싫었던 건...
because...
왜냐면
the way that you run
is just a little....
네가 달리는 모습이 좀...
-So?
-It's embarrassing.
그래서?
남들이 미쳤다고
생각하면 창피하잖아
People were looking at us
like we were crazy.
무슨 상관이야?
-Why do you care?
-Because they're people!
남들이니까
People you don't know
and will never see again.
모르는 사람들이잖아
다시 볼 것도 아니고
그래도 남이야
눈까지 달렸고
Yes, but still they are people...
with eyes.
I didn't get embarrassed
running next to Miss....
난 네가 이렇게 뛰어도
창피하지 않아
But okay.
오, 그렇구나
I can see why running with me
would be embarrassing to you.
너한테는 왜 그런 게
문제가 되는지 알겠다
Okay. You're uptight.
맞아, 넌 꽉 막힌 애야
What? I am not uptight.
뭐?
내가 왜 꽉...
보세요, 난 절대...
I am not uptight, man.
막히지 않았네, 이 사람아
That's okay. I'm not judging you.
That's just who you are.
괜찮아, 이건 비난이 아니라
사실이 그렇다는 거야
I'm more free, you know.
I run like I did when I was a kid...
난 좀 더 자유롭지
어렸을 때부터
난 그렇게 뛰었어
because that's the only way
it's fun, you know?
그게 재미있으니까, 알아?
Didn't you ever run so fast
you thought your legs would fall off...
꽁무니가 빠져라
뛰어본 적 없니?
그네를 향해 달려가거나
사탄한테 쫓길 때
Like when you were running towards
the swings or running away from Satan?
The neighbor's dog.
동네 개 이름이야
Is this in the right place?
이 램프 제대로 놓였냐?
Who cares? I repel women.
알 게 뭐야
여자들이 난 싫다는데
안 돼, 들어오지 마
You can't come in here!
Ross is naked!
로스가 홀랑 벗었어
- 뭐?
- 뭐야?
I couldn't say I was naked,
because she's allowed to see me naked.
내가 벗었다고 하면
들어와도 되잖아
Why does anyone have to be naked?
왜 누가 홀랑 벗어야 되는데?
Why is Ross naked?
왜 오빠가 벗고 있는 거야?
I had to show Chandler something.
챈들러한테 보여줄 게 있어서
Naked?
다 벗고?
아무래도 나한테...
I guess I have...
a "guy" problem.
남자만의 문제가 있는 듯해서
Is it the same thing
Chandler had?
챈들러랑 같은 문제야?
We'll get everything squared away,
and you can come back later!
저기, 조금만 있다 와
금방 해결할 테니까 기다려
There's still some of Chandler's
medicine in the bathroom.
알았어, 챈들러가 먹던 약이
욕실 세면대 밑에 있을 거야
-Bye.
-Bye!
- 이따 봐
- 잘 가
Thank God.
살았다
Dude, what'd you have?
너 무슨 병인데?
We have no time, okay?
We must focus.
야, 시간 없으니까 서둘러서
전부 제자리에 돌려놔야 돼
We've got to get everything
back into its original place.
The photo album!
사진첩
There were millions of pictures
of the apartment in the photo album.
이 집에서 찍은 사진이
엄청나게 많잖아
사진을 참고해서
제자리를 찾으면 되지
We just match everything
to the pictures!
That's perfect! That's brilliant!
- 멋진 생각이다
- 그래
넌 천재야
What'd you have?
진짜 무슨 병이야?
I've got some beer for you.
왔군요, 이 맥주 먹어요
여기선 '마셔요'라는
표현이 정확하겠죠?
Don't you mean "for whom"?
Sure.
그렇네요
I was gonna order some pizza.
You wanna share one?
피자 주문할 건데
같이 먹을래요?
피자라, 그런 거 못 먹어본
사람도 있을까, 버럼범 피시
Pizza? It's not like I never
had that before.
Is something wrong?
무슨 일 있어요?
Yeah. I'm depressed about that
Irish potato famine.
네, 아일랜드 감자 기근이
날 슬프게 하는군요
우리 말이에요, 내 앞에선
행동이 좀 이상해져요
No, I mean with me. Because you seem
to be acting really weird around me.
All right, all right.
좋아요
Let's just get this
out in the open, okay?
터놓고 얘기합시다
괜찮죠?
You're hot.
당신은 예뻐요
I'm lovable.
난 사랑스럽고
Clearly, there's a vibe
going on between us.
분명 우리 사이에
뭔가 진행되고 있죠
하지만 우린 룸메이트예요
But we're roommates...
and it's a huge mistake
for us to continue down this road.
이 길을 계속 가는 건
큰 실수라 이거죠
- 조이...
- 아니, 들어봐요
Imagine living in a supermarket...
당신이 슈퍼마켓에 산다고
생각하면 이해가 될 거예요
and you'll understand.
Okay? So the question is,
what do we do?
그럼 이제 우리가
어떡하면 좋겠어요?
어떻게 하고 말 것도 없죠
물론 당신은 좋은 사람이지만
There isn't anything to do.
I think you're really sweet.
But I'm not interested
in you like that.
그런 쪽에는 관심 없어요
No, I mean....
아니, 내 말은...
You're a nice guy, and I'm happy
to be your roommate and your friend.
당신은 괜찮은 사람이고
룸메이트로서 친하게
지내는 건 좋지만
I'm just, you know, I just...
난 그냥... 알잖아요
그런 느낌은 없다는 거예요
don't feel that way about you.
아, 왜 그런지 알겠다
I see what happened.
It's because I was trying
to repel you.
내가 일부러 정을
떼려고 했기 때문이죠
Right? Believe me, you'd feel
a lot different if I turned it on.
틀림없어요
내가 제대로만 하면
상황 완전히 역전입니다
-I don't think so.
-Oh, I do.
- 글쎄요
- 두고 봅시다
How you doing?
안녕하쇼?
I'm okay.
그럼요
What?
네?
뭐가요?
Oh, dear God!
환장하겠네
- 안녕!
- 그래, 안녕!
미안해, 네가 맞았어
진짜 기분 좋아
I'm so sorry. You're right.
This feels great!
거봐, 남들 의식할 거 없어
한 번 지나가면 끝이거든
And you don't care if people stare.
It's only a second. Then you're gone!
끝이지
정말 신난다
It's amazing!
I feel so free and so graceful!
너무나 자유롭고
마음이 편해
안녕, 말 조심하세요
Watch out for the horse.
죄송합니다
- 이제 들어가도 돼?
- 응
Can I come in now?
- 분위기가 달라졌네?
- 안녕
-Why is everything different?
-Bye.
달라진 건 하나도 없는데
I don't see anything different...
other than the fact that the room
got brighter when you came into it.
자기가 들어오니까
방이 환해진 거 말고는
The end table is wrong,
the couch looks bizarre...
탁자랑 소파 위치도 이상하고
냉장고 자석은 보기도 싫어
and don't even get me started
on the refrigerator magnets.
제발 화내지 마
Okay, don't be mad, okay?
박스를 다 정리한 후에
자기를 기쁘게 해주고 싶어서
After I unpacked the boxes, I wanted
to do something nice for you...
so I cleaned the apartment.
내가 아파트를 청소했어
전부 다 들어내다 보니
제자리가 어딘지 잊어버렸어
So I moved everything around,
and then I forgot...
where it went back.
I'm sorry, I'm very sorry, I'm sorry.
정말 송구스럽습니다
괜찮아
That's okay.
Are you afraid of me or something?
자긴 내가 무서운 거야?
Do you want me to be afraid of you?
야단 안 칠 거야?
Of course not.
말도 안 돼
My gosh, Chandler, what you did
is a wonderful thing...
이렇게 마음 써준 게
얼마나 고마운 일인데
and I really appreciate it.
틀어진 물건은 모두
제자리에 갖다 놔야겠지만
I have this thing where I want
everything in the perfect place.
자기가 그런 걱정을 왜 해
But I'd never expect you
to worry about that.
Really?
진짜?
Of course.
그럼
Oh, you're the best.
역시 자기가 최고야
You come here to me.
이리 와봐
Hold on, okay?
First things first.
- 잠깐만 기다려
- 그래
이것부터 처리하고
좋아, 이제...
오빠가 옷 벗고
어디 앉은 적 있어?
Did Ross sit anywhere
while he was naked?
It said that by the year 2030...
다가오는 2030년에는
컴퓨터가 실제 인간의 뇌와
똑같은 능력을 갖게 된대요
there'll be computers carrying
out the same number of functions...
as an actual human brain.
이론적으로만 보면
인간의 생각과 기억을
So, theoretically, you could
download your thoughts...
컴퓨터에 저장시켜서
and your memories
into this computer..
And live forever as a machine.
영원히 살 수 있겠네요
근데...
Janine, do you know
what we're doing right now?
재닌, 지금 이게
뭔지 알겠어요?
당신과 내가 접속된 거예요
You and I, we're interfacing.
I gotta go.
난 이만 갈게요
버럼범 피시